I'm at the beauty parlor.
I'm going to make my first public appearance tomorrow.
It's a fitting.
I'm going to do it at the same time as Hiiichan.
What a surprise.
It's a uniform.
That's why we'd like to do the fitting.
The voice actors have already gathered today.
Ta-da!
Ready, set, go!
This time...
Timo asked us to make AKB-like uniforms.
I thought it might be a good idea to make a uniform that's stiff and flat, like an AKB uniform...
But after a little discussion with Timo...
I was thinking of changing the uniform for each program.
I was thinking of changing the uniforms for each show.
Everyone who listened to the show was amazed.
You're strangling yourself by saying that.
They're so busy, but they're willing to do that.
You know... AKB fans...
AKB has been doing a lot of shows and stuff.
Every time we do a show or something, they react to our outfits.
Even when they were wearing lip gloss, they got really excited about the costumes.
And the members are very casual about it, too.
So, in order to create a topic of conversation every time.
The members also tell us about the new costumes this time.
or "This is the theme for this show.
Every time, the members are able to send out a message.
If we could take pictures every time on Footalk or Instagram or something like that...
It would be a great source of material for YouTube.
Every year, every year, every time, every time, every time, every time, every time...
That's great!Why don't you just ask for it and send it out?
We can bring you all kinds of uniforms.
All the Japanese people, including me, love it.
A little bit of the same theme
to match the character.
Just by looking at these pictures
I can tell that it's really Mogi-chan just by looking at the outfit.
I can tell just by looking at the outfit that it's hers.
Yurimiru is not the type to show her skirt
That vest is often used by me.
Or you can wear a jacket like that.
I'll decide at the fitting.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, I'll go change.
I'm having the shirt adjusted so that it fits nicely in the vest.
The shirt has this emblem embroidered on it.
It's a cute shirt.
The original vest. It's very stylish.
I like vests.
I'm the only one with a vest that's long. Mori and I are the only two with vests that are long.
But they're cute. That's my vest.
They'll all give you one.
Emblems are coming around. I'm glad.
I'm glad. It's quite chic here.
It's for idols. I think it's cute.
I think it's cute. I think this color looks good on you, too.
That color, too, for sure.
Thanks for your hard work.
Put out a lot.
You too.
Oh, here it is.
How's it going?
You're one of those people, aren't you?
I don't know.
Very satisfied.
Very satisfied with the remote.
Rough it up.
Just a little bit.
Remote from here.
Best
Big winner
Thank you very much.
You're so cute.
Ta-da!
So, the first live performance of Kampdan TV Live is just about over, and it looks like this.
This is how it's going to be? I've been reading your Twitter feed and you've been saying all kinds of things... like the witch's ping-pong ring.
I'm glad you're a lady, but I don't know why there were so many of you...
I'm glad to see that you're a lady-like girl, but for some reason there were a lot of people who thought that Takamina had inherited a big ribbon.
I didn't mean it that way at all, because Naru-chan also inherited a ribbon of the exact same size and color.
That wasn't the intention. Mr. Kinoshita prepared it.
I can't believe this is the first time I've seen you in this outfit.
I can't believe it. I'm surprised. I'm looking forward to the next show, where we'll get to wear different uniforms.
So, everyone, please give my best to the new song "I Can't Help Liking You.But today, the song is only a minute and a half long, so they made it for only a minute and a half .
I want to take a picture of it.
If you want to try dancing, this is the best choice right now. Puzzle Rhythmination.
My hair is straight today.
The number is different, old lady.
Mel's weather is like this.
I'm going to Kabuki now.
We have an interview today.
I'm going to introduce you to some of the costumes for the Bazurismo.
Today is the last day of the single period, and today is the last day of the Osaka Uta-Kon, which will be aired in Osaka.
And since it's the last one, we're going to show you the new costumes for the Uta-Kon today.
This time it's pastel!
The theme is pastel, pink, gray, and light blue.
The theme is pastel, pink, gray, and light blue!
It's so cute, so cute, so cute.
Seriously, they're all cute, they're always cute, but they're really cute!
Here it is!
It's so cute!
It's cute either way.
I'll see what I can do with it.
I'll try one at a time.
I put them on the zucchini loader.
Not even close.
Poof!
Cute. Isn't it close? Look at the shape.
It sure is. Vest?
Vest?
I see.
There's a difference between a high-street ribbon and a string ribbon.
It's amazing.It's totally different.
It's like we're going down a different road.
I'll be back in Osaka to show you the finished product, including the hair.
Please look forward to it.
Today is the live broadcast of the Singing Contest.
Here's the last of the new look.
It looks like this.
The socks have been changed.
They've been changed to ones with lines in them.
The hair ornament...
It has a pretty ribbon.
Ribbons and pints are now attached.
The overall shape is much more mature.
The memory is also
It's cute!
With ribbon and pinto
Overall, it's a more mature shape
Memory too.
It's so cute!
The members are adorable.
And the staff.
They make me look good.
Thank you.
So, which uniform was your favorite?
I think I'd have to go with the Buzz Rhythm Marine or this one.
They're all cute, but
I like pastel colors, which is my favorite.
I didn't wear my hair up even once this time.
I don't know...
There were a lot of girls around me who wore their hair up.
I'm very, very happy with all the outfits I got!
If you have a favorite outfit, please leave a comment!
We made it through the uniform period!
So thank you all for watching!
See you soon!
I had to whisper because everyone was in the dressing room.
[ED]
undefined